Academy Athletic Fes
مهرجان الأكاديميّة الرّياضي
Come on, hurry up!
!هيّا، بسرعة
Up first is...
...الأوّل هو
Light music club, the stage is yours.
نادي الموسيقى الخفيفة، المسرح لكُم
Athletic Festival Closing Ceremony Change Clothes and Head to the After-Party!
مراسم اختتام المهرجان الرّياضي تغيير الملابس والتوجّه إلى حفلة ما بعد الحفلة
Episode Twelve I'm Not Alone
الحلقة الثّانية عشر لستُ وحيدة
First-Years The Winners Are...
طالبات السّنة الأولى ...الرّابح هو
That was awesome!
!كان ذلك مذهلاً
You were amazing!
!كنتُما رائعتين
Thank you!
!شكراً
Okay!
!حسناً
Is everyone enjoying the after-party?
هل يستمتع الجميع بحفلة ما بعد الحفلة؟
Yeah!
!أجل
Oh, yeah! We're getting warmed up now!
!أجل! سنقوم بالإحماء الآن
Next is the highly-anticipated performance by the drama club!
فيما يلي الأداء المُرتقَب بشدّة !بواسطة نادي الدراما
Who's performing?
من سيؤدّي؟
Oh, Usagihara-san.
أوساغيهارا-سان
This year's performance is by just one first-year member!
!الأداء لهذا العام تقوم به مجرّد طالبة سنة أولى
And that first-year is the girl who's been the talk of the whole school...
وطالبة السّنة الأولى هذه الّتي أمست ...حديث النّاس في المدرسة كلّها
You wiped off all the sweat?
مسحتِ كلّ العرق؟
Yeah.
أجل
She always says hi to anyone she makes eye contact with.
تقول مرحباً دوماً لأيّ شخص تتلاقى عيناه معها
Once you see that sailor uniform, you know it's her.
حالما ترون زيّ البحّارة الرّسميّ ذاك، ستعرفون بأنّها هي
You're up as soon as the broadcasting club girls say your name.
ستنطلقين حالما تُعلِن فتاتا نادي البثّ عن اسمكِ
Yeah.
حسناً
Are you nervous?
هل أنتِ متوتّرة؟
A little.
قليلاً
You'll be fine. If anyone can do this, it's you.
ستكونين بخير. إن كان هناك مَن يستطيع القيام بهذا، فهو أنتِ
I'll be rooting for you, too.
سأشجّعكِ أيضاً
Okay!
!حسناً
Can you all guess who it is?
هل يمكنكم جميعاً أن تُخمّنوا من تكون؟
Okay, come on out.
حسناً، اخرجي
I can't hear anything.
لا أستطيع سماع شيء
It's like I'm underwater.
وكأنّني تحت الماء
Thanks for your time.
شكراً لوقتك
She was all for the accompaniment idea, huh?
كانت مؤيّدة بشدّة لفكرة التّرافُق، صحيح؟
I was surprised when she told me to play right then and there.
تفاجأتُ عندما قالت بأنّها ينبغي ،أن يكون ترافُقاً أمام الملأ
So, um... thanks.
إذاً... شكراً
For lending me the CD, too.
على إعارتي الأسطوانة أيضاً
It's fine. Akebi-chan will be thrilled.
لا عليكِ. ستتحمّس أكيبي-تشان كثيراً
The song you're dancing to
الأغنية التي سترقصين عليها
has a piano accompaniment, right?
سيُرافقها عزف بيانو، صحيح؟
Yeah! I love that piano part!
!أجل! أحبّ فقرة البيانو تلك
What if you could dance to a live piano accompaniment at the after-party?
ماذا لو استطعتِ الرّقص بمُرافقة بيانو على الهواء في حفلة ما بعد الحفلة؟
What?
ماذا؟
I can't even imagine something that amazing.
لا أستطيع حتّى أن أتخيّل شيئاً مذهلاً كهذا
I can't even imagine it.
لا أستطيع تخيّله حتّى
Those steps...
...هذه الخُطى
Fight on!
!إلى الأمام
They're the same ones she used for her cheer!
!إنّها نفس خُطاها عندما كانت تُشجّع
Akebi-san was constantly running.
كانت أكيبي-سان تجري بلا توقّف
I only ever saw her from behind as she sprang off the ground, but now...
لم أرها إلّا من الخلف عندما قفزت ...مسرعة من الأرض، لكن الآن
Darn it, I'm such an idiot.
تبّاً، يا لي من حمقاء
I can't even see Komichi-san from here.
لا أستطيع حتّى رؤية كوميتشي-سان من هنا
But that's fine.
لكن لا مُشكلة
I can just remember.
يمكنني أن أتذكّر فحسب
Because ever since this morning...
...لأنّه منذ هذا الصّباح
I can do that move, too.
يمكنني أداء تلك الحركة أيضاً
You did spend all that time practicing with her.
قضيتِ كلّ ذلك الوقت تتمرّنين معها
Akebi-chan was always...
...لطالما كانت أكيبي-تشان
No one could've received it way over there!
مُحال أن يتمكّن أحد من استلامها هناك
Hotaru-chan! You don't have to cry!
!هوتارو-تشان! لا يجوز أن تبكي
After a game that awful...
...بعد مُباراة فظيعة كتلك
All along...
...من البداية
...she was...
...كانت...
...cheering us on.
تُشجّعنا...
And now, it's our turn.
والآن، حان دورنا
Akebi
أكيبي
I can hear them cheering for me.
يمكنني سماعهن يُشجّعنَني
Final round, lane 1: Class 1-3.
الجولة الأخيرة، المسار 1: الصفّ 3-1
Go, go!
!هيّا، هيّا
You can do it!
!يمكنكِ فعلها
Keep it up!
!واظبي على ذلك
Ohkuma-san!
!أوكوما-سان
Go!
!هيّا
Tatsumori-san! Fight on!
!تاتسوموري-سان! إلى الأمام
Komichi, it doesn't matter what place you finish in.
كوميتشي، لا يهمّ المركز الّذي تنتهين إليه
Thanks for the concern!
!شكراً على الاهتمام
Okay, I'm gonna get out there and work up a sweat!
!حسناً، سأسبح إلى هناك وأبذل جهدي
Akebi-san, you can do it!
!أكيبي-سان، يمكنكِ فعلها
Komichi-san!
!كوميتشي-سان
Akebi-san!
!أكيبي-سان
You've got this!
!يمكنكِ فعلها
Go, Riri-san!
!هيّا يا ريري-سان
Riri-san! Fight on!
!ريري-سان! إلى الأمام
You can do it!
!يمكنكِ فعلها
Go!
!هيّا
First place! Class 1-3 takes first place!
!المركز الأوّل! يحتلّ الصفّ 3-1 المركز الأوّل
I couldn't have done it on my own.
ما كنتُ لأستطيع فعلها بمفردي
I'm not alone.
لستُ وحيدة
Komichi-san is always surprising me.
دائماً ما تُفاجئني كوميتشي-سان
From the moment we met right up until today.
منذ لحظة لقائنا حتّى اليوم
Fukumoto Miki
فوكوموتو ميكي
It switches to violin toward the end.
تنتقل للكمان في أواخرها
The only reason I was able to enjoy playing like this again...
السّبب الوحيد وراء قدرتي على الاستمتاع ...بالعزف هكذا من جديد
was because of Komichi-san.
كان كوميتشي-سان
It's the last event!
!إنّه الحدث الأخير
Hurry up!
!بسرعة، بسرعة
It's the final round!
!إنّها الجولة الأخيرة
Go!
!هيّا
You can do it!
!يمكنك فعلها
Keep calm!
!حافظي على هدوئك
Man, this is wreckin' my nerves.
هذا يُتلِف أعصابي
Go, Riri!
!هيّا يا ريري
Receive!
!إرسال
We lost our lead... because of me.
خسرنا تقدّمنا... بسببي
Sorry—
—آسفة
That was a nice dive.
كانت قفزة ممتازة
Komichi!
!كوميتشي
Keep fighting!
!كافحي
Keep your spirits up as high as Komi's!
!لا تدعنَ طاقة كومي تغلبكن
We're gonna take this last set!
!سنربح في المجموعة الأخيرة هذه
Let's win this!
!لنحقّق النّصر
I have to keep it in the air!
!عليّ إبقاؤها في الهواء
Minakami-san returned it! But...
...أعادَتْها ميناكامي-سان! لكن
The rally's still going!
!ما زال تبادُل الرّميات مستمرّاً
It's not over yet!
!لم ينتهِ الأمر بعد
Komi!
!كومي
There's no way I could mess up.
من المُحال أن أخفق
I mean...
...أعني
I was able to do that, after all.
تمكّنتُ من فعل "ذلك" أساساً
I did... that!
!"فعلتُ... "ذلك
Akebi-chan!
!أكيبي-تشان
Akebi-chan! Kizaki-san!
!أكيبي-تشان! كيزاكي-سان
Akebi-san!
!أكيبي-سان
That was great!
!كان ذلك ممتازاً
Thank you, Erika-chan.
شكراً لكِ يا إيريكا-تشان
Winners Class 1-3
الرّابح الصفّ 3-1
Monday Snooze Dismiss
الإثنين قيلولة تجاهل
Onee-chan, you're finally awake!
!أونيه-تشان، استيقظتِ أخيراً
What time is it?!
!كم السّاعة؟
So I woke up before you today.
استيقظتُ قبلكِ اليوم إذاً
Breakfast is ready.
الفطور جاهز
I'll be right there!
!أنا قادمة
It kinda feels like it was all a dream...
...أشعر وكأنّ كلّ ذلك كان حلماً
Want a ride partway there?
أتريدين توصيلة إلى منتصف الطريق؟
That's okay! I'm used to running!
!لا مشكلة! أنا معتادة على الجري
You've got everything?
هل أخذتِ كلّ شيء؟
Yep!
!أجل
Onee-chan!
!أونيه-تشان
Your collar's flipped up.
ياقتكِ غير مضبوطة
Thanks!
!شكراً
Well, I'm off!
!حسناً، سأغادر
Hey, Komichi!
!كوميتشي
Taira-san! Good morning!
!تايرا-سان! صباح الخير
One, two... One, two...
...واحد، اثنان... واحد، اثنان
Hey, we're starting!
!سوف نبدأ
Ready!
!استعداد
Swimming Club
نادي السّباحة
Mountaineering Club
نادي تسلّق الجبال
Tennis Club
نادي كرة المضرب
Table Tennis Club
نادي كرة الطاولة
I was waiting for you.
كنتُ أنتظركِ
Winners Class 1-3
الرّابح الصفّ 3-1
That was so much fun.
كان ذلك ممتعاً للغاية
Yeah, it was.
أجل، بالفعل
Think we'll ever get to do it again?
أتعتقدين بأنّها سنفعلها من جديد يوماً ما؟
Sure we will. Lots of times.
بالتأكيد. سنفعلها مرّات كثيرة
Morning!
!صباح الخير
Winners Class 1-3
الرّابح الصفّ 3-1